ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American Bar Association Committee on Committees, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- American Bar Association Committee on Development of Law of Union Administration, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- American Bar Association Committee on Pension, Welfare and Related Plans, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- American Bar Association Committee on Practice and Procedure, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- American Bar Association Special Committee on Specialization of the ABA, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- American Bar Association Committee on Wage Stabilization, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- American Bar Association General Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- American Bar Association Rothman and Hein, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- American Bar Association Standard Operating Procedures, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- American Bar Association Voting Procedures, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- American Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- American Express Records, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Anti-Defamation League, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Association of Private Pension and Welfare Plans, Pensions, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Cornell Appropriations Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Cornell Board of Trustees, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Cornell Board of Trustees, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Jewish Labor Committee Action File, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Jewish Labor Committee Action File, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Jewish Labor Committee Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Jewish Labor Committee Correspondence, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Jewish Labor Committee Correspondence, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- International Rescue Committee Semi-Annual and Annual Meeting Notices and Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- International Rescue Committee General Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Hebrew Immigrant Aid Association General Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council Joint Program Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- PACE College, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Public Employee Relations Board, 1970-1977 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Public Employee Relations Board- Mount Kisco, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Public Employee Relations Board- Other, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Public Employee Relations Board- Payments, 1970-1972 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Public Employee Relations Board- Publications, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- ACWA- Political Activity Individuals, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- ACWA- Political Activity General, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Actuaries, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Blue Collar Workers, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Bonds and Bonding, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Disclosure, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Fiduciary, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- General, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council General (Permanent), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Minutes of Meetings, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Foreign Pensions, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Private Pensions, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Termination, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- US Department of Labor Advisory Council- Travel, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Rochdale Institute, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- J. Sheinkman Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 2], 1972-1976 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- J. Sheinkman Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 2], 1972-1976 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- J. Sheinkman- Telephone Messages. [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- J. Sheinkman- Telephone Messages. [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Ahlers, Adolf, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Secretary Treasurers Book, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Association of Private Pension and Welfare Plans- Business Statements, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- J. Bernstein and Sassenberg Property Sale, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Frasca- Estate of Luigia, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- R. Hill, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- R. Mayer, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Federal Bar Association of New York, New Jersey and Connecticut, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Fried- Estate of Milton (Probate), 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Brandzel and Atlas- Property Sale, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Caban, Killmer and Giaccone- Property Sale, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Community Insurance Exchange, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Hennepin- Paper Company, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- G. McGovern, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- J. Messina, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Motor Vehicle Accident Industry Corporation, 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Montezinos, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- R. Schaeffer, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- F. Rosenblaum, 1969-71 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Skelley and Augenblick, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Union Label and Service Trade, 1974-1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- E, J. Sheinkman Ltd., 1967-1970 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Memorandums- J. Sheinkman to Department Heads, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- United Housing Foundation, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  July to December
- United Housing Foundation, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  January- June
- United Housing Foundation, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  May- December
- United Housing Foundation, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  January- May
- Resumes, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Resumes, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Resumes, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- OSHA, 1972-1976 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Organizing Department- General, 1973-1976 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- J. Sheinkman Message Sheets. [Folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- J. Sheinkman Message Sheets. [Folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Memos, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Imports, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Imports- Wolf and Co., 1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Imports, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Imports Statements, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Imports Reports, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Industrial Union Department- Committee Recommendations, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Imports Reports, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Imports, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Imports Statements, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Imports, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Import Study File, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  June
- Import Study File, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Mortgage Investment Trust, 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Printed Matter, 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Secretary- Treasurers Conference, 1973-1977 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Industrial Union Department Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department Correspondence, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Industrial Union Department Organizing, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Industrial Union Department- Report on Examination, 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Industrial Union Department- Special Committee, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Industrial Union Department- Transition Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Industrial Union Department- US Raw Material Policy, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries- Insurance Fund, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund- Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance- Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company Inc.- Financial Reports, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company Inc.- Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated- New York Plant, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- R. Straiss Trade Negotiations, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- J. Sheinkman Trade Negotiations, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  Apr.-June
- J. Sheinkman Trade Negotiations, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- J. Sheinkman Trade Negotiations, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  July- September.
- ACTWU Staff Reports, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- British North America Committee, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  Oct.- Aug.
- British- North America Committee, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- J. Sheinkman Christmas Regrets, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- J. Sheinkman Christmas Cards (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Clippings- General, 1976-1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Contributions- Priority, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  Aug.- Dec.
- Contributions- Priority, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  Apr.- July
- Contributions- Priority, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Contributions- Priority, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  Sept.- Dec.
- Contributions- Priority, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  Mar.-Sept.
- Contributions- Priority, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  Jan.-April
- ACWA- Control Department, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Control and Industrial Department, 1976-1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Conservation of Human Resources Report (Drennan), 1977 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Consumer Protection Act, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Convention, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Committee on Appeals and Grievances, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Convention Unity, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Convention Delegates, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Convention Guest Lists, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Convention- Miscellaneous Materials, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Convention Press Releases, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Convention Resolutions, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- ACWA Convention- Washington DC, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- GEB Agenda and Minutes, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- ACWA Convention- Guests and Honored Guests, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Wolf and Co. Imports Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- V. Miller Materials, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- ACWA Political Convention, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- ACTWU Resolutions, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Union Label Materials, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- ACWA Convention- Administration and Committee Reports, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- ACWA Convention- Miscellaneous Materials, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- ACWA Convention- Constitution and Resolutions, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- ACWA Convention- Honored Guests and Guests, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- ACWA Convention- Speech Material, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Coordinated Bargaining Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- COPE, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Cotton Negotiations, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Cotton Negotiations- Single Pants, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Cotton Negotiations- Shirts, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Cotton Negotiations- Outerwear, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Cotton Garment Industry Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Cotton Negotiations Outerwear, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Cotton Negotiations- Shirts, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Cotton Negotiations- General, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Redevelopment Proposals, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Council on the Economy of New York City, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Economic Development Board Demographic Analysis, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Economic Development Board Executive Committee Action, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Economic Development Board Executive Committee, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Economic Development Board- Governors Message, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Economic Development Board Reports, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Economic Development Board Resolutions, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Economic Development Board: Report on Unemployment insurance. [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Economic Development Board: Report on Unemployment insurance. [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  Contains official reports/memos
- Economic Development Board: Report on Unemployment insurance. [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  Discussion and Memos regarding report.
- Economic Development Board: Report on Unemployment insurance. [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  All copies of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America proposal for Unemployment Insurance solvency. March 1976
- Economic Development Board NYS: State Environmental Quality Review, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Economic Development Board NYS: Jacob Sheinkman Testimony, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  Before the Labor Committee of the Senate of New York, October 16, 1975.
- Economic Development Board: Tax Study, 1975-1977 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Economic Development Board: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Economic Development Board: Projects (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Economic Development Board: Reports, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Blue Copies, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  September - December, 1977.
- Correspondence: Blue Copies, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  January - August, 1977.
- Correspondence: Blue Copies, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  January - December, 1976.
- JLC Germany Trip Correspondence: Blue Copies, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Economic Development Board: Action File, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Economic Development Board: Action [folder 1 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Economic Development Board: Action [folder 2 of 3], 1977 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Economic Development Board: Action [folder 3 of 3], 1977 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Economic Development Board Action File, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Economic Development Board: NYS Budget, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  January 21, for February 4th Meeting.
- Economic Development Board: NYS Background Material, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  Includes Empire State Report, September and October 1975
- Economic Development Board/ Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  Memos, letters, reports relating to the EDB
- Economic Development Board: Executive Committee, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  Memos and letters to the committee, also reports studying 1975-1976
- Economic Development Board: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1976 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Economic Development Board: Committees and Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  Contains memos/reports about meeting, October 1975 Meeting report.
- ECB Development and Planning; Article 19-K, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  Act introduced by NYS senate committee of rules, March 25th
- Economic Policy Council-UNA [1 of 6], 1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Economic Policy Council-UNA [2 of 6], 1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Economic Policy Council-UNA [3 of 6], 1977 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Economic Policy Council-UNA [4 of 6], 1977 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Economic Policy Council-UNA [5 of 6], 1976 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Economic Policy Council-UNA [6 of 6], 1977 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  More 1977 Material, June/July
- Economic Policy Council-UNA, 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- George Solomons, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  Memo/Financial reports directed at George Solomons
- South Korean Textile Workers, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  Letters
- Special Strike and Organizing Fund., 1976-1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  Financial records
- Southern Wage Agitation Drive., 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  Memos and Reports from Sol Stetin
- Sol Stetin Testimonial Banquet, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  Planning materials, invitations, donor list, discussion.
- J.P. Stevens Contract-1980 Agreement (Box 52, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  Union memos, discussion of campaign to organize
- J.P. Stevens, 1976-1980 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  Discussion of boycott; legality; tactics used during campaign; letters of congratulation to union.
- Stevens Boycott Department, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  Memos regarding leverage over J.P. Stevens
- ACTWU Synthetic Fibers and Film Division, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  Memos; Letters; Newspaper clippings; discussion of Union Label Industry Show.
- Textile ACTWU-Charges and Strike Authorizations, 1976-1979 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  Charges filed against union members; Sol Stetin authorizing local union strikes.
- Textile Industry Reports, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  Sent to ITGLWF, June 1978, Israel
- Textile-Merger with AWCA (Post Merger), 1978-1980 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  Memos regarding Merger
- ACTWU Retirement & Pension Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  Memos
- Textile Division-Canadian Office, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  Memos; Newspaper clippings
- Tikun, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  Small Amount of Yiddish
- International Trade and Investment, (Art Gundershiem file) [2 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  Memos regarding International trade; Union cooperation; Imports and exports and effect on union
- International Trade and Investment, (Art Gundershiem file) [1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  Legislation proposals; Memos
- Tufts University, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  Communication Between Union and Tufts
- Union Label., 1980 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  Memos regarding activities and department personal
- Union Pension Fund Investment Advisory Board, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  Reports; Memos regarding formation of Board
- Union of Post Office Workers (U.K.), 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  Letters Between Tom Jackson and Jacob Sheinkman
- Unions Other then ACTWU, 1975-1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  Communications between other unions and ACTWU; Jacob Sheinkman
- 15 Union Square Renovations, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  Memos regarding repairs; Cost estimates; Progress reports
- Union Square Realty, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  Memos and Contracts regarding Union Square property development; Audited Financial statements for 1978
- United Automobile Workers, 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  Communications Between UAW Leadership and Jacob Sheinkman
- United Farm Workers, 1973-1976 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  Communications between ACTWU and United Farm Workers; UFW memos; UFW Newspaper clippings
- United Federation of Teachers, 1976-1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  Communications between UFT and Jacob Sheinkman
- United Garment Workers of America, 1977-1980 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  UGWA Tax returns; Communications with Jacob Sheinkman; Dispute between ACWTU and UGWA
- United Hatters Cap & Millinery Workers, 1974-1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  May extend to 1970 or 1980. International Communications; Legal documents; Statement by Gerald Coleman.
- United Housing Foundation, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  Financial communications regarding retirement plan
- United Housing Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  Retirement benefits applications; Financial reports; Invoices
- United Jewish Appeal, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  Fund-raising letter, November 13th
- United Mine Workers, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  Letters and Funding from ACTWU to United Mine Workers; Jacob Sheinkman
- United Nations Association of the United States of America 1980 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  Letters; Memos; Agendas; Research papers relating to UNA-USA
- UNA Board of Governors, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  Memos; Reports; Meeting minutes
- UNA-Economic Policy Council, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  Memos; Policy Reports; Letters; Grain related
- UNA-Economic Policy Council, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  Memos; Reports; Publications
- UNA-Economic Policy Council` Trade Panel, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  One letter from 1981; Research & Policy Reports, Memos; Letters
- UNA-International Trade Affairs, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  Report by Royal Institute of International Affairs; Letter regarding same from Jacob Sheinkman
- UNA North American Economic Area Policy, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  Research and Policy report, letters regarding same
- UNA Policy Studies Committee, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  Report giving an overview of the Committee's work, August 7, 1980
- United Paper Workers Union, 1974-1979 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  Communications from Jacob Sheinkman regarding the UPWU
- United Rubber Workers, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  Memos; Letters; Donations
- Countervailing Duty, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  Regarding Foreign subsidies to their exports, ACWU letters regarding same
- Credit Union, 1974-1980 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Criminal Code Bill H.R. 6233, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  Letters between Jacob Sheinkman and Rep. Peter Rodino, Jr.
- Cross Country, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  Research reports
- Curbell, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  Memos regarding strikers receiving union strike benefits and state UI
- Misc Folder, "D", 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  Donlin dispute, newspaper clippings, articles
- Damon Creations, 1975-1980 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  Letters and Memos between Damon Creations and ACWU
- Dunlop- Computer Pull out, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- William DuChessi Scholarship, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  Letters; Memos, Reports; Records
- DunLop Labor/Management Committee, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Dunlop Study, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  Study on effects of imports; Letters; Memos; Reports regarding same
- Dunlop Study Training Program, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  Research Report, year uncertain
- E Misc, 1974-1980 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  Encampment for Citizenship; Eagle Clothing; Ernst & Whinney; other assorted memos and letters
- Economic Consulting Service, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  Report regarding imports
- Economic Development Advisory Council- Felix G. Rohatyn, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  Communications between Rohatyn and the EDAC, NYS Governor Carey
- Economic Development Board Action File, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Economic Development Board Action File, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  Research reports; Newspaper clippings
- Economic Development Board Executive Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  Memos; Reports
- Economic Development Board Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  Reports; Memos; Letters; Newspaper clippings
- Edcar Industries, Inc, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  Proposed agreement between Union and Edcar Industries, January 13, 1975
- Edison Electric Institute, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  Memos regarding Jacob Sheinkman's speech at Labor Relations Conference, May 15-16, 1979
- The Educational Alliance inc., 1978 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  Speaking invitation, April 14, 1978
- ACTWU Education, 1976-1981 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  Letters; Memos; Reports regarding ACTWU education related communications and conferences
- Bruce Raynor Report, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  Unions in the Southern Textile Industry
- Education-Field Staff Programs, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  Evaluation of conference
- Egyptian Textile Workers Union, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  Aly M. Dofdaa
- Dr. Ehrenberg Visit, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  Memos; Letters
- Employee Benefit Research Institute, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  Discussion Forum record and findings
- Employee Relations Law Journal, 1977-1979 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  Communications regarding Journal; Jacob Sheinkman
- Enro-At-Ease Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  Memos; Letters; Cost reports; Newspaper clippings
- ACTWU-ERISA/Department of Labor, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  Memos, letters regarding alleged violation of ERISA by the ACTWU
- Ernst and Whinney, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 8)